Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2007
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2007
Mus. Arc. 38
Haupt, Irene
11 CD-ROMS (248 digital images)
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
Contains 248 digital images (tiff files) of musicians who participated in the June in Buffalo Festival 2007 at the University at Buffalo.
Administrative Information
Terms of Access
Materials can be examined by qualified researchers in the Music Library during hours of operation during which Music Librarians are present. In order to insure access, researchers are advised to contact the Music Library in advance of visits.
Acquisition Information
Purchased from Irene Haupt, 2007.
Accruals and Additions
No further accruals are expected to this collection.
Alternate Forms
130 images from the June in Buffalo 2007 collection are included in the University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.
Biographical Note
Irene Haupt, a graduate of the State University of New York at Buffalo, has been documenting the Buffalo arts scene through her photography since 1976. During that time she has worked for, or with, some of the most notable institutions in Buffalo, including the Irish Classical Theatre, Studio Arena Theater, the Kavinoky Theatre, the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, the Theatre of Youth, the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, and the State University of New York at Buffalo. In addition to her specialty of theater photography, Irene Haupt has also devoted much of her career to the photography of musicians and musical events. Most notable is her documentation of the contemporary music scene in Buffalo, including coverage of the University at Buffalo's June in Buffalo festival of new music, 1982-1987, and 2000 to the present. Over the course of those years, she has created a visual record that contains images of some of the most significant composers and performers of the last quarter century. The list of names is impressive: Aaron Copland, Morton Feldman, Leo Smit, Virgil Thomson, Steve Reich, Ralph Shapey, Henry Brant, Earle Brown, Ursula Oppens, Jan Williams, Lukas Foss, Philip Glass, Otto Luening, Conlon Nancarrow, Ernst Krenek, Larry Austin, Lejaren Hiller, Elliott Carter, Milton Babbitt, John Cage, Charles Wuorinen, Jacob Druckman, and Yvar Mikhashoff, among others.
The June in Buffalo festival of contemporary music was begun at the University at Buffalo in 1975 by composer Morton Feldman. He directed the festival 1975-1978 and in 1980. The festival was dormant from 1981 through 1985. David Felder revived the festival in 1986 and has been its director since that time.
Scope and Content Note
The collection of Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2007 contains 248 images of participants in the festival for 2007. The list of musicians includes David Felder, Roger Reynolds, Steve Reich, John Harbison, Charles Wuorinen, Arditti String Quartet, Harold Rosenbaum, Lucy Shelton, Curtis Macomber, Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble, Steve Schick, Alan Feinberg, Nicholas Isherwood, and Tony Arnold.
Arrangement
Eleven series, one for each CD-ROM. Series titles are transcriptions of markings on the CD-ROMS.
I. CD-ROM 1. June in Buffalo 07
II. CD-ROM 2. June in Buffalo 2
III. CD-ROM 3. JIB 2007-3
IV. CD-ROM 4. JIB-07
V. CD-ROM 5. Steve Reich rehearsal
VI. CD-ROM 6. Reich & Reynolds, RFBF
VII. CD-ROM 7. RFBR [sic]
VIII. CD-ROM 8. Reynolds masterclass '07
IX. CD-ROM 9. Lucy Shelton
X. CD-ROM 10. Harbison masterclass
XI. CD-ROM 11. Felder Chasmal, Reynolds The Palace, JIB '07
Container List
- June in Buffalo 07, June 2007, I.; 1 CD-ROM (12 image files in TIFF format)
  Files are numerically arranged by intermediate, assigned file names. Original file names are included for reference.
  - Arditti Quartet violinist Ashkot Sarkissian with student composer Bert Van Herck, Original file name: -Arditti workshop- -------.tif (Image-file cd01_01)
  - Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, Ashkot Sarkissian, Ralf Ehlers, Lucas Fels) on stage in Baird Recital Hall with student composer Dominique Schafer, Original file name: ARDITTI WORKSHOP 07.tif (Image-file cd01_02)
  - Arditti Quartet violinists Irvine Arditti and Ashkot Sarkissian with student composer Bert Van Herck, Original file name: Arditti workshop----.tif (Image-file cd01_03)
  - Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, Ashkot Sarkissian, Ralf Ehlers, Lucas Fels) with student composer Bert Van Herck, Original file name: Arditti workshop_---------.tif (Image-file cd01_04)
  - Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, Ashkot Sarkissian, Ralf Ehlers, Lucas Fels) with student composer Bert Van Herck, Original file name: JIB 07 workshop Arditti.tif (Image-file cd01_05)
  - Irvine Arditti with student composer Dominique Schafer, Original file name: o7 Arditti Workshop.tif (Image-file cd01_06)
  - Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, Ashkot Sarkissian, Ralf Ehlers, Lucas Fels) on stage in Baird Recital Hall with student composer Dominique Schafer, Original file name: stud.composer Arditti workshop.tif (Image-file cd01_07)
  - Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, Ashkot Sarkissian, Ralf Ehlers, Lucas Fels) on stage in Baird Recital Hall with student composer Dominique Schafer, Original file name: Workshop Arditti -x.tif (Image-file cd01_08)
  - Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, Ashkot Sarkissian, Ralf Ehlers, Lucas Fels) with student composer Bert Van Herck, Original file name: Workshop Arditti Quartet --.tif (Image-file cd01_09)
  - Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, Ashkot Sarkissian, Ralf Ehlers, Lucas Fels) with student composer Bert Van Herck, Original file name: Workshop Arditti Quartet -.tif (Image-file cd01_10)
  - Arditti Quartet violist Ralf Ehlers and violoncellist Lucas Fels with student composer Bert Van Herck, Original file name: workshop Arditti-.tif (Image-file cd01_11)
  - Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, Ashkot Sarkissian, Ralf Ehlers, Lucas Fels) on stage in Baird Recital Hall with student composer Dominique Schafer, Original file name: x Arditti workshop.tif (Image-file cd01_12)
- June in Buffalo 2, June 2007, II.; 1 CD-ROM (53 image files in TIFF format)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish percussionist Johannes Fischer playing bass drum, Original file name: - Johannes Fischer.tif (Image-file cd02_01)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble, with director Steve Schick, composer Lee Weisert, Justin DeHart?, and Matthew Jenkins, rehearsing Weisert's composition Rockaby, Original file name: ---..RFBF--.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-052 (Image-file cd02_02)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble members Ross Karre, Robert Esler, Steve Schick, and Fabio Oliveira rehearsing Charles Wuorinen's Percussion Quartet, Original file name: --RFBF--.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-056 (Image-file cd02_03)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble members Justin DeHart, Matthew Jenkins, and Fabio Oliveira rehearsing Ya-Ting Lee's composition, Ritual, Original file name: --RFBF.tif (Image-file cd02_04)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble members Justin DeHart, Matthew Jenkins, Johannes Fischer, and Fabio Oliveira rehearsing Ya-Ting Lee's composition, Ritual, Original file name: -.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-054 (Image-file cd02_05)
  - Percussionist Steven Schick rehearsing solo sections of Part I of Roger Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: -Steve Schick.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-104 (Image-file cd02_06)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish percussionist Johannes Fischer playing bass drum, Original file name: ...Johannes Fischer.tif (Image-file cd02_07)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish percussionist Fabio Oliveira playing bass drum, Original file name: ...tif (Image-file cd02_08)
  - Johannes Fischer playing the bass drum, Original file name: ..Johannes Fischer....tif Converted file name: JIB2007-018 (Image-file cd02_09)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish percussionist Johannes Fischer playing bass drum, Original file name: ..Johannes Fischer.tif (Image-file cd02_10)
  - Student composers Aaron Helgesen and Fusun Koksal with Arditti Quartet violoncellist Lucas Fels and violist Ralf Ehlers, Original file name: Aaron Helgeson=Fusun Koksal in ARDITTI workshop.tif (Image-file cd02_11)
  - Arditti String Quartet with workshop participants, Dominique Schafer, Trevor Bjorklund, Carmel Raz, Aaron Helgeson, Fusun Koksal, and Bert Van Herck, Original file name: ARDITTI QUARTET and student composers.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-004 (Image-file cd02_12)
  - Arditti String Quartet in rehearsal, Original file name: ARDITTI quartet workshop.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-001 (Image-file cd02_13)
  - Arditti Quartet (Irvine Arditti, Ashkot Sarkissian, Ralf Ehlers, Lucas Fels) on stage, Original file name: ARDITTI quartet.tif (Image-file cd02_14)
  - Student composers Aaron Helgesen and Fusun Koksal with Arditti Quartet violinist Irvine Arditti, Original file name: Arditti workshop Aaron Helgeson Fusun Koksal.tif (Image-file cd02_15)
  - Student composer Aaron Helgesen with Arditti Quartet violinist Ashkot Sarkissian and violoncellist Lucas Fels, Original file name: Arditti workshop Aaron Helgeson.tif (Image-file cd02_16)
  - Arditti Quartet violist Ralf Ehlers with student composer Fusun Koksal, Original file name: ARDITTI workshop Fusun Koksal.tif (Image-file cd02_17)
  - Arditti Quartet violinist Irvine Arditti with student composer Trevor Bjorklund, Original file name: Arditti workshop....tif (Image-file cd02_18)
  - Audience at Arditti Quartet workshop in Baird Recital Hall, including John Harbison, Original file name: ARDITTI workshop.tif (Image-file cd02_19)
  - David Felder gesturing during masterclass, Original file name: DAVID FELDER.tif (Image-file cd02_20)
  - David Felder gesturing during masterclass, Original file name: FELDER masterclass-x.tif (Image-file cd02_21)
  - David Felder gesturing during masterclass, Original file name: FELDER masterclass--.tif (Image-file cd02_22)
  - Student composers at David Felder masterclass, Original file name: Felder masterclass.tif (Image-file cd02_23)
  - Composer Fusun Koksal with violist Ralf Ehlers, Original file name: Fusun Koksal in ARDITTI workshop.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-041 (Image-file cd02_24)
  - Student composers Aaron Helgesen and Fusun Koksal with Arditti Quartet violoncellist Lucas Fels and violist Ralf Ehlers, Original file name: Fusun Koksal-Aaron Helgeson=ARDITTI QUARTET.tif (Image-file cd02_25)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish percussionist Johannes Fischer playing bass drum, Original file name: Johannes Fischer.tif (Image-file cd02_26)
  - Student composer Lee Weisart with Red Fish Blue Fish percussionists Steve Schick and Justin Dehart(?), Original file name: Lee Weisert and RFBF.tif (Image-file cd02_27)
  - Student composer Lee Weisart with Red Fish Blue Fish percussionists Steve Schick, Justin Dehart(?), and Matthew Jenkins, Original file name: Lee Weisert and RFBF.tif (Image-file cd02_28)
  - Tony Arnold, vocalist, and Christian Baldini, conductor, rehearsing Paolo Cavallone's Scendero a patti with ensemble of Sabatino Scirri, flute, Rin Ozaki, percussion, Will Chapin, guitar, and Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Original file name: Paolo Cavallone SCENDERO A PATTI.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-007 (Image-file cd02_29)
  - Tony Arnold, vocalist, and Christian Baldini, conductor, rehearsing Paolo Cavallone's Scendero a patti with ensemble of Sabatino Scirri, flute, Rin Ozaki, percussion, Will Chapin, guitar, and Jonathan Golove, violoncello, Original file name: Paolo Cavallone.tif (Image-file cd02_30)
  - Percussionist Steven Schick with composer Lee Weisert, rehearsing Weisert's composition, Rockaby, Original file name: RFBF -Lee Weisert stud.composer.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-105 (Image-file cd02_31)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble members Justin DeHart and Fabio Oliveira rehearsing Ya-Ting Lee's composition, Ritual, Original file name: RFBF---.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-055 (Image-file cd02_32)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble members Justin DeHart, Matthew Jenkins, Fabio Oliveira, and Johannes Fischer rehearsing Ya-Ting Lee's composition, Ritual, Original file name: RFBF--.tif (Image-file cd02_33)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble members Ross Karre, Robert Esler, Steve Schick, and Fabio Oliveira, Original file name: RFBF.tif (Image-file cd02_34)
  - Rin Ozaki bowing a gong, Original file name: Rin Ozaki---.tif (Image-file cd02_35)
  - Rin Ozaki bowing a gong, Original file name: Rin Ozaki.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-050 (Image-file cd02_36)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish percussionists Justin DeHart and Fabio Oliveira rehearse Ya-Ting Lee's Ritual, Original file name: RITUAL by Ya-Ting Lee.tif (Image-file cd02_37)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds onstage with the Arditti String Quartet after a performance of Reynolds's composition, Ariadne's thread, Original file name: Roger Reynolds and Arditti.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-090 (Image-file cd02_38)
  - Stage setup for percussion used in Roger Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: Roger Reynolds SANCTUARY stage.tif (Image-file cd02_39)
  - Stage setup for percussion used in Roger Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: Stage SANCTUARY.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-112 (Image-file cd02_40)
  - Percussionist Steven Schick rehearsing solo sections of Part I of Roger Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: Steve Schick in SANCTUARY....tif Converted file name: JIB2007-101 (Image-file cd02_41)
  - Percussionist Steven Schick rehearsing solo sections of Part I of Roger Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: Steve Schick in SANCTUARY...tif Converted file name: JIB2007-102 (Image-file cd02_42)
  - Percussionist Steven Schick rehearsing solo sections of Part I of Roger Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: Steve Schick in SANCTUARY.tif (Image-file cd02_43)
  - Composer Roger Reynolds adjusting microphone for percussionist Steven Schick during rehearsal of Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: Steve Schick- Roger Reynolds.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-085 (Image-file cd02_44)
  - Percussionist Steven Schick rehearsing solo sections of Part I of Roger Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: Steve Schick-.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-100 (Image-file cd02_45)
  - Percussionist Steven Schick rehearsing solo sections of Part I of Roger Reynolds's composition, Sanctuary, Original file name: STEVE SCHICK.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-103 (Image-file cd02_46)
  - Composer Fusun Koksal with violinist Irvine Arditti and violoncellist Lucas Fels, Original file name: stud.composer Fusun Koksal -Arditti.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-040 (Image-file cd02_47)
  - Jonathan Golove performing on violoncello while composer Jane Stanley watches (rehearsal of her work, Deep turn), Original file name: stud.composer Jane Stanley DEEP RUN.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-020 (Image-file cd02_48)
  - Arditti String Quartet with workshop participants, Dominique Schafer, Trevor Bjorklund, Carmel Raz, Aaron Helgeson, Fusun Koksal, and Bert Van Herck, Original file name: student composers and ARDITTI QUARTET.tif (Image-file cd02_49)
  - Johannes Fischer performing with bass drum, Original file name: x-Johannes Fischer RITUAL by Ya-Ting Lee.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-019 (Image-file cd02_50)
  - Student composer Ya-Ting Lee at rehearsal with Red Fish Blue Fish percussion group, Original file name: YA-Ting Lee at rehearsal....tif (Image-file cd02_51)
  - Student composer Ya-Ting Lee at rehearsal with Red Fish Blue Fish percussion group, Original file name: YA-Ting Lee at rehearsal.tif (Image-file cd02_52)
  - Composer Ya-Ting Lee, Original file name: Ya-Ting Lee student composer.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-042 (Image-file cd02_53)
- JIB 2007-3, June 2007, III.; 1 CD-ROM (12 image files in TIFF format)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble, with director Steve Schick (lower left), Ross Karre, Johannes Fischer, Justin DeHart, Robert Esler, Fabio Oliveira, Ian Sexton, and Matthew Jenkins, with the Waterphone used in Roger Reynolds's composition Sanctuary, Original file name: ORACLE with RFBF 07.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-051 (Image-file cd03_01)
  - Steve Schick and members of Red Fish Blue Fish in discussion with audience after concert, Original file name: RFBF talk with audience after concert.tif (Image-file cd03_02)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble, with director Steve Schick (lower left), Ross Karre, Johannes Fischer, Justin DeHart, Robert Esler, Fabio Oliveira, Ian Sexton, and Matthew Jenkins, with the Waterphone used in Roger Reynolds's composition Sanctuary, Original file name: RFBF with Roger Reynolds Oracle 07.tif (Image-file cd03_03)
  - Student composer Daniel Blake with Red Fish Blue Fish percussionists Johannes Fischer and Ross Karre, Original file name: RFBF with student comp.Daniel Blake.tif (Image-file cd03_04)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble members Robert Esler and Fabio Oliveira rehearse Daniel Van Hassel's composition, Trudge Blasted Exotic, Original file name: RFBF-Daniel VanHassel TRUDGE BLASTED EXOTIC.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-058 (Image-file cd03_05)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble members Robert Esler and Fabio Oliveira rehearse Daniel Van Hassel's composition, Trudge Blasted Exotic, Original file name: RFBF.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-059 (Image-file cd03_06)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish percussionists Robert Esler and Fabio Oliveira, Original file name: Robert Esler-Fabio Oliveira RFBF.tif (Image-file cd03_07)
  - Steve Schick in discussion with audience after concert, Original file name: Steve Schick and RFBF lecture after concert.tif (Image-file cd03_08)
  - Steve Schick and members of Red Fish Blue Fish in discussion with audience after concert, Original file name: Steve Schick and RFBF talking to student composers.tif (Image-file cd03_09)
  - Composer Daniel Van Hassel watches as Red Fish Blue Fish Percussion Ensemble members Fabio Oliveira and Robert Esler rehearse Van Hassel's composition, Trudge Blasted Exotic, Original file name: student composer Daniel Blake-RFBF.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-057 (Image-file cd03_10)
  - Red Fish Blue Fish percussionists Ross Karre and Johannes Fischer performing work by James Ogburn, Original file name: Student composer James Ogburn -RFBF.tif (Image-file cd03_11)
  - Student composers listening to Red Fish Blue Fish post-concert lecture.tif, Original file name: student composers listening to RFBF talk.tif (Image-file cd03_12)
- JIB-07, June 2007, IV.; 1 CD-ROM (46 image files in TIFF format)
  - Charles Haupt, Rin Ozaki, and Tony Arnold, Original file name: 001 Charles Haupt Rin Ozaki Tony Arnold.tif (Image-file cd04_01)
  - Charles Haupt, Rin Ozaki, and Tony Arnold, Original file name: 002 Charles Haupt -Rin Ozaki-Tony Arnold.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-027 (Image-file cd04_02)
  - Charles Haupt, Tony Arnold, and Rin Ozaki rehearsing John Aylward's End of winter, Original file name: 006 END OF WINTER by John Aylward Tony Arnold Rin Ozaki Ch~1.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-029 (Image-file cd04_03)
  - David Felder in masterclass with student composers, Original file name: 044 Masterclass David Felder.tif (Image-file cd04_04)
  - David Felder in masterclass with student composers, Original file name: 048Masterclass David Felder.tif (Image-file cd04_05)
  - David Felder in masterclass with student composers, Original file name: 049 Masterclass David Felder.tif (Image-file cd04_06)
  - David Felder in masterclass with student composers, Original file name: 051 Masterclass David Felder.tif (Image-file cd04_07)
  - June in Buffalo students Jeff Silva, Daniel Van Hassel, and Jacques Baldasari, Original file name: 052 Masterclass David Felder.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-115 (Image-file cd04_08)
  - Student composers in David Felder masterclass, Original file name: 053 Masterclass David Felder--=.tif (Image-file cd04_09)
  - David Felder in masterclass with student composers, Original file name: 053 Masterclass David Felder.tif (Image-file cd04_10)
  - David Felder examining score with students Aaron Helgeson, Jane Stanley, Eliza Brown, and Michael McBride, Original file name: 054 Masterclass David Felder.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-015 (Image-file cd04_11)
  - David Felder commenting on a score, with students Michael McBride and Jane Stanley, Original file name: 055 Masterclass David Felder.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-016 (Image-file cd04_12)
  - Arditti String Quartet posing onstage, Original file name: Arditti quartet rehearsal.tif (Image-file cd04_13)
  - Arditti String Quartet posing onstage, Original file name: ARDITTI Quartet 018.tif (Image-file cd04_14)
  - Arditti String Quartet posing onstage, Original file name: ARDITTI Quartet 019.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-003 (Image-file cd04_15)
  - David Felder with the Arditti String Quartet during rehearsal of Felder's String Quartet no. 2, Original file name: ARDITTI Quartet and David Felder 009.tif (Image-file cd04_16)
  - David Felder with the Arditti String Quartet during rehearsal of Felder's String Quartet no. 2, Original file name: ARDITTI Quartet and David Felder 010.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-013 (Image-file cd04_17)
  - David Felder with the Arditti String Quartet during rehearsal of Felder's String Quartet no. 2, Original file name: ARDITTI Quartet and David Felder 011.tif (Image-file cd04_18)
  - David Felder with the Arditti String Quartet during rehearsal of Felder's String Quartet no. 2, Original file name: ARDITTI Quartet and David Felder 015.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-014 (Image-file cd04_19)
  - Composer Christian Baldini with conductor Harold Rosenbaum rehearsing Baldini's composition, Two adoration motets, Original file name: Christian Baldini_ Harold Rosenbaum.tif (Image-file cd04_20)
  - Tony Arnold, Paolo Cavallone, and Christian Baldini, Original file name: Christian Baldini_ Tony Arnold stud.comp.Paolo Cavallone.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-006 (Image-file cd04_21)
  - Composer Christian Baldini with conductor Harold Rosenbaum and members of the New York Virtuoso Singers rehearsing Baldini's composition, Two adoration motets, Original file name: Christian Baldini_The NY Virtuoso Singers.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-098 (Image-file cd04_22)
  - Student composers looking at David Felder score during rehearsal, Original file name: David Felder Lecture score.tif (Image-file cd04_23)
  - Students David Hanner (right), John Aylward, and Fusun Koksal examining a score during a lecture by David Felder, Original file name: David Felder lecture---.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-021 (Image-file cd04_24)
  - David Felder examining score with students Jeff Silva, Daniel Blake, and Dominique Schafer, Original file name: David Felder Lecture-.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-017 (Image-file cd04_25)
  - Student composers in audience for David Felder lecture, Original file name: David Felder Lecture.tif (Image-file cd04_26)
  - David Felder during seminar, Original file name: David Felder masterclass.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-009 (Image-file cd04_27)
  - Student composer looking at David Felder score during rehearsal, Original file name: David Felder score-.tif (Image-file cd04_28)
  - David Felder during seminar, Original file name: FELDER masterclass-x.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-010 (Image-file cd04_29)
  - David Felder during seminar, Original file name: FELDER masterclass--.tif Converted file name: JIB2007-011 (Image-file cd04_30)
  - Student composers in David Felder masterclass, Original file name: Felder masterclass.-.tif (Image-file cd04_31)
  - Student composers in David Felder masterclass, Original file name: FELDER masterclass.tif (Image-file cd04_32)